

## (KG) Keiji Kaneko

Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd. - General Director/President

Connect

**♠** Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



### Connect

**△** Message

• • •

## (KG) Keiji Kaneko

Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd. - General Director/President Vietnam · 38 connections · **Contact info** 

Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Universtity of Wisconsin - Eau Claire

People and pages related to (KG) Keiji

See all

X

**>** 



Cargill

Page • Food Production 1,487,595 followers

#### **Follow**



## Food Safety, Microbiology and Hygiene

Page • Food Production 49,250 followers

#### **Follow**



#### Institute of Food Technologists (IFT)

Page • Non-profit Organization Management 107,465 followers

#### **Follow**

### About

32 years after the completion of MBA program in Dec., 1988, among those, 18 years of experience working in overseas (outside Japan). In developed countries, developing countries, as various postion in the company, being successful of working with local staff & achieved remarkable business expansion and renovation.

## Activity

54 followers

Posts (KG) Keiji created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

See all activity

## Experience

#### **General Director/President & Chairman**

Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd. Jul 2017 – Present

#### **CEO and Managing Director**

Ajinomoto (Malaysia) Berhad Jul 2015 – Jun 2017 • 2 yrs Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

During 2-year term, increased stock price more than 3 times.

#### **Director, Sales and Operations - Sweeteners**

Ajinomoto Food Ingredients LLC Oct 2008 – Jul 2011 · 2 yrs 10 mos Chicago, USA

Managed Global Accounts (Beverage, Confectionary & Foods) for sweeteners.

Developed new Local accounts to apply Sweeteners.

In charge of Business Development of new Sweetener.

#### **Managing Director**

West African Seasonings Co., Ltd.
Jul 2004 – Jul 2007

· 3 yrs 1 mo
Lagos, Nigeria

Packaging, Sales and Marketing company. 100% subsidiary of Ajinomoto Co. Inc. Being as Managing Director for three years, Revenue had increased more than twice and turned into black figure in Operating Profit.

Honored as one of the distinguished performers of the year among Ajico Group. in 2005.

## **Branch Manager and Director of Domestic Consumer Products**

Ajinomoto Sales Indonesia Jul 1994 – Jul 2001 · 7 yrs 1 mo Surabaya and Jakarta, Indonesia

4 yrs as Branch Manager in Surabaya Branch, which covers the half of Indonesian country.

Promoted to Director of Domestic Consumer Products Division, being responsible for the national Sales organization and Marketing.

## Education

## **Universtity of Wisconsin - Eau Claire**

Skills & endorsements 事業戦略 損益管理 経営 Other Skills 👩 サプライチェーン管理 マーケティング Show less ^ Accomplishments Languages インドネシア語 ・ 日本語 ・ 英語

Interests

**University of Wisconsin-Eau Claire** 

62,438 followers



# People also viewed



THÚY Phạm Thị Thanh •3rd

Assistant Brand Manager – Aji-Quick® Crispy Flour and Complete Seasoning at Ajinomoto Vietnam Co Ltd.

Connect

Hung Ho Tan •3rd

Media and External Relation at Ajinomoto Vietnam

Connect



Loan Phan •3rd+

Manager Account at Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Connect



Hanh Nguyen •3rd

Supervisor at Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Connect



Trang Tran •3rd+

Supply Chain Senior Executive at Ajinomoto Vietnam Co., Ltd.

Connect

**Show more Show more** 

# People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



**Nhi Duong** 

Connect		
<b>∨</b> Show more		
in LEARNING		
Add new skills with these courses		
Building and Managing a High-Performing Sales Team		
20,367 viewers		
Business Development: Strategic Planning		
115,565 viewers		
Supply Chain Basics For Everyone		
66,744 viewers		
	Show more on LinkedIn Learning	
Linkod		
Linked in		
About		
Accessibility		
Talent Solutions		
Community Guidelines		

Student at Ton Duc Thang University

Careers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms ✓	
Ad Choices	
Advertising	
Sales Solutions	
Mobile	
Small Business	
Gafety Center	
Questions?	
/isit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy	
Go to your Settings.	
Select Language	
(Arabic) العربية	
inkedIn Corporation © 2021	
	C

